(Sheldon:)Stop yelling.
(Sheldon:)I'm not happy about this.
(Leonard:)What's the last thing
you were ever happy about?
(Sheldon:)The prospect of fried chicken.
(Mrs Cooper:)This is exciting.
(Mrs Cooper:)Back home, the diner
on Route 4 serves sushi...
(Mrs Cooper:)...but it's just cut up fish sticks
and a side of Uncle Ben's.
(Mrs Cooper:)They put it on the menu in those kung fu
Ietters, but that don't make it sushi.
Uh, "Kung fu letters"
might not be politically correct.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, I thought the one
we couldn't say was "ching chong."
(Leonard:)Yeah, yeah, that too.
(Mrs Cooper:)So, Shelly, what's up with you
and your friend Amy...
(Mrs Cooper:)...if you don't mind
a mother prying a bit?
(Sheldon:)Well, there's actually big news
on the Amy front.
(Sheldon:)She's been studying the neurobiology
of addiction in lower animals.
She's this close to getting a starfish
hooked on cocaine.
(Mrs Cooper:)You have any idea
what's going on with those two?